Arkadiusz Sarach

Junior Front-End Developer



Personal Info

Email

arkadiusz.sarach@gmail.com

Address

Cracow

Phone

604 368 995

GitHub

https://github.com/Ajek1993

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/arkadiusz-sarach/

Skills

Programming languages: JavaScript

(Node.js), CSS, SCSS

Frameworks/Libraries: React, Next.js, Tailwind CSS, Material UI, NextUI

IDE: Visual Studio Code

Other: Git, Firebase, MongoDB

Languages

English - B2

Hobby/Interest

music (playing drums), literature (Sapkowski, Cejrowski, astronomy), sport (cycling), computer games Determined to change the industry to IT, I am constantly willing to develop and acquire new knowledge. I quickly learn technical issues and can effectively apply them in practice. Since I started learning, I have experienced great satisfaction from discovering new possibilities offered by the latest libraries and frameworks. This is an additional motivation for me to improve in this field. The most inspiring projects for me are those that make use of the potential of the latest technologies. I am particularly fascinated by creating working algorithms that solve problems.

Projects

Fleet Manager

https://github.com/Ajek1993/Fleet_Manager

Web aplication to manage car's fleet - allows adding/removing cars, repairs, fuel, counting costs.

Technologies: React, Material UI, Firebase, Firestore, git

Oddaj Rzeczy

https://github.com/Ajek1993/OddajRzeczy

One page site - allows sending forms to data base.

Technologies: Next.js, Tailwind CSS, Firebase, Firestore, git

Education

2023-12

2023-12	wode.js for programmers
- present	Coders Lab - Szkoła IT
	Duration - 13 hours
2023-03	Front-End-Developer
- 2023-10	Coders Lab - Szkoła IT
	Duration - 180 hours
2013-10	Mining geomechanics and underground construction, Master
- 2018-10	of Science

Node is for programmers

Work History

2019-07 - present	Branch supervisor Stava S.A., Kraków
2017-04 - 2019-06	Driver Abacus Sp. z o.o., Kraków
2015-07 - 2015-08	Intern Polska Grupa Górnicza - KWK "Piast-Ziemowit" - Ruch Piast, Bieruń

Akademia Górniczo-Hutnicza im. Stanisława Staszica, Kraków

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie danych osobowych zawartych w niniejszym dokumenciedo realizacji procesu rekrutacji zgodnie z ustawą z dnia 10 maja 2018 roku o ochroniedanych osobowych (Dz. Ustaw z 2018, poz. 1000) oraz zgodnie z RozporządzeniemParlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawieochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawieswobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (RODO).